http://www.orchardrecovery.com/privacy/

Privacy Policy Home » Privacy PolicyWho are weOrchard Recovery Center is https://orchardrecovery.com and all subdomains associated with orchardrecovery.comYour privacy is very important to us.At Orchard Recovery Center we have a few fundamental principles that we follow:We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, or to protect our rights.We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of our site.Website VisitorsLike most website operators, Orchard Recovery Center collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, general region the visitor is browsing from and the date and time of each visitor request. Orchard Recovery Center’s purpose in collecting non-personally-identifying information is to better understand how Orchard Recovery Center’s visitors use it’s website.Orchard Recovery Center also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, names and email addresses through the use of contact forms and website chat (Intercom).Gathering of Personally-Identifying InformationCertain visitors to Orchard Recovery Center’s website choose to interact with Orchard Recovery Center in ways that require Orchard Recovery Center to gather personally-identifying information.  The amount and type of information that Orchard Recovery Center gathers depends on the nature of the interaction.  Orchard Recovery Center does not disclose personally-identifying information to any third party organization.  Any website visitor can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website related activities.Contact FormsBy filling out a contact form and requesting email contact with Orchard Recovery Center we ask visitors to provide a name, email address and consent to store this information.  If consent is obtained from the website visitor the browser information and IP address is also stored on our site.  This information will be stored for at most 30 days before it is automatically deleted from our servers.Web ChatBy using the web chat widget to request contact with Orchard Recovery Center the website visitors general location, browser information, last page viewed, date of first and last visit will be stored. Optionally website visitors can leave their email address so that communication will continue both on the web and via email.  The entire website conversation will be stored until it is manually deleted after approximately ninety (90) days.  This information can be accessed by Orchard Recovery Intake specialists. Orchard Recovery Center uses the Intercom chat widget for this form of communication and all information related to the chat is stored on their servers. For more information about the Intercom chat widget please see their privacy policy at https://www.intercom.com.EventsOrchard Recovery Center occasionally puts on events that require registration to participate (due to limited seating). In those cases we request name, email address and phone number so that we can confirm registration and send update information should it be required.  This personally-identifying information will be stored on our servers until the event has completed at which time it will be deleted.Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying InformationOrchard Recovery Center discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of it’s employees and contractors that:Need to know the information in order to process it on Orchard Recovery Center’s behalf or to provide services available at Orchard Recovery Center’s website.That have agreed not to disclose it to others.Some of the employees and contractors may be located outside of your home country; By using Orchard Recovery’s website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.Orchard Recovery Center will NOT rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone.Other than to its employees and contractors, as described above, Orchard Recovery Center discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other government request, or when Orchard Recovery Center believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Orchard Recovery Center or the public at large.If you have provided your email address through a contact form, web chat or event registration, Orchard Recovery Center will NOT use that email address for any other purpose other than replying to your question.Orchard Recovery Center takes all measure reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.CookiesA cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitors browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Orchard Recovery Center uses cookies to help Orchard Recovery Center identify and track visitors and their usage of Orchard Recovery Center’s website.Orchard Recovery Center visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computer should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Orchard Recovery Center’s website, with the drawback that certain feature of Orchard Recovery Center’s website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.Cookies that are used on Orchard Recovery Center website (but are not limited to) are by Google Analytics, Facebook, Facebook Pixel and Intercom.Please visit their specific privacy pages to determine their cookie usage.Google – https://policies.google.com/privacyFacebook – https://www.facebook.com/policy.phpIntercom – https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policiesExternal LinksOrchard Recovery Center provides some links external to Orchard Recover Center’s website. Orchard Recovery Center has NO control of any content, cookies, tracking, advertising, etc on an external website and caution should be used before clicking on an external link. Please visit the particular external links privacy page before clicking on a link.Privacy Policy ChangesAlthough most changes are likely to be minor, Orchard Recovery Center may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and at Orchard Recovery Centers sole discretion. Orchard Recovery Center encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy.  Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes.Contact About Privacy PolicyIf you have questions about this privacy policy, would like information on any personally-identifying information that are stored on our servers, our would like your personally-identifying data deleted please call our toll free number: 1-866-233-2299 or Email Privacy Officer.Orchard Recovery will comply with your request as soon as possible (normally within 5 business days).Contact About WebsiteIf you have questions about this website please call our toll free number: 1-866-233-2299 or Email Website Administrator.Orchard Recovery Center Privacy Policy updated: December 21, 2018
